CURRICULUM VITAE

CHIRAYU J. PATHAK

B.PHARM, M.PHARM, DIM, PGDIM, PGDOM, MBA

Contact No. 09327358827 (M)

E-mail: kul_chirayu1@yahoo.co.in, cjpathak1@gmail.com



PROFILE SUMMARY:

Around 11 years of Experience in Pharmaceutical Industry (10 years experience in R&D Project Management and 1 year in Regulatory Affairs). Excellent communication & team management skills with high levels of self-motivation and ability to pour this in team.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Cadila Healthcare Limited – Pharmaceutical Technology Centre (PTC) Feb 2016 to Till Date
Associate Manager, R&D- Project Management (PMT)

Project Management of US Projects (Solid Orals, Transdermal, Controlled substance products)

- To prepare budget, establish work priorities, monitoring deadlines are met and procedures are followed.
- ➤ Prepare and execute the project work plan and revise it as appropriate as and when required and align with management.
- To support in arranging timely availability of resources required during product development.
- ➤ Co-ordination with cross functional departments (Portfolio team, F&D, ADL, PD, PK, Purchase team, Plant planning team, validation cell, Production, Pkg, QC, QA, stability cell, Regulatory team, legal, Outside labs, CROs, etc.) for smooth execution of projects.
- Aligning with various stakeholders for timely availability of API, raw materials, reference products, licenses (Form-11, Form 29 NoC, Form-29, Procurement NoC and NCB licenses), tooling, API techpack/ o-DMF, special capex requirements at manufacturing sites, etc.
- > Conducting weekly & bi-weekly meetings along with various R&D functions and relevant CFT teams to have updates on projects tasks completion, foreseeing issues, appropriate escalation and resolution.
- ➤ Preparing and submitting to senior management the MIS periodically including update on projects, matters requiring their attention and implementing their decisions (monthly, quarterly, half yearly & annually).
- ➤ Collecting and analyzing data associated with projects undertaken to ensure timely deliverables of projects within scope and budget.
- Managing work associated with Overseas Subsidiaries, CROs and service providers for project development and report on variations to work assigned to them.

Chirayu J. Pathak Page 1 of 6

- Resourcefully managing MIS of Scale-ups & exhibit batches executions across all manufacturing locations (Solid Oral, Injectable, Topical, Transdermal & Pulmonary dosage forms) on monthly basis and aligning with senior management for addressing the concerns for timely & smooth executions of batches.
- > Organize annual budget for the Scale-up & exhibit batches to be taken across various sites for resource planning & also the 5 years forecast for capacity mapping at all mfg sites and coordinating with site planning team for the same.
- ➤ Collating analytical method validations (AMV) to be performed month on month across all validation sites and ensuring and confirming the planning of the same on monthly basis.
- ➤ Coach, mentor, motivate and supervise project team members, and persuade them to take positive action and accountability for their assigned work.
- ➤ Have managed projects for India market with varied dosage forms viz. Solid orals, Liquid orals, Ophthalmic, Injectable, Pulmonary, Dietary supplements (biscuits, powder, etc.), Cosmetics (cream, shampoo, soap) in various category like DCGI filing, commercial launch, in-licensing, etc.
- ➤ Contributing to the in-house project management tool.

Torrent Research Centre, Bhat, Gandhinagar

Jun 2013 to Jan 2016

Executive (Project Coordinator), R&D- Project Management (Product Development Group)

Project Management of Brazil/US/EU and Russia Projects

- To ensure smooth and timely development of projects
- To prepare budget for the project life cycle with respect to timelines and resources required.
- To do resource planning and management throughout the project life cycle by coordinating with various departments within research & development center /and also with Plant, HO, marketing, suppliers, overseas subsidiaries /customers/ CROs.
- Mapping project plan, prepare management presentations and reports periodically.
- Establish work priorities, ensure deadlines are met and procedures are followed.
- > To review market extension feasibility of a product to other countries depending upon time needed of development and filing requirements as per regulatory guidelines.
- > Planned and successfully executed de-risking of Brazil under approval/ commercial products as part of Brazil business regularization.

Famy Care Ltd., SEZ, Ahmedabad

Dec 2012 to Jun 2013

Executive (Project Coordinator), R&D-Project Management

Project Management of US/EU/Brazil and ROW Projects

Chirayu J. Pathak Page 2 of 6

- ➤ Manage and coordinate projects, tasks, schedules, and status to support effective decisions and project reporting to stakeholders.
- Ensuring processes are in place and effectively used. Ensure problems resolved and escalate as appropriate.
- ➤ Delegate tasks and responsibilities to appropriate personnel.
- Manage changes to project timelines, ensure that all impacts and changes are approved and appropriately communicated to stakeholders.
- Monitor projects on a weekly basis to identify and mediate conflicts based on changes to project time lines.
- ➤ Identify and resolve issues and conflicts within the project team.
- > Track project milestones and deliverables.
- ➤ Coach, mentor, motivate and supervise project team members, and influence them to take positive action and accountability for their assigned work.
- ➤ Handled and successfully completed internal audit of R&D store by finance department.

Cadila Pharmaceuticals Ltd., Dholka, Ahmedabad

Jan 2012 to Dec 2012

Executive, Regulatory Affairs (MENA & SEA countries)

- > To ensure preparation and submission of product compliance file for all new registrations and reregistrations to support smooth execution of export orders.
- > Preparation and submission of registration and re-registration dossiers as per International marketing requirements.
- Ensure good documentation practice within the department.
- ➤ Review of technical documents received from various departments in line with current regulatory guidelines.
- Timely reply to various queries from the Regulatory authorities.
- Enhance self awareness about changing regulatory requirements.
- Establish co-ordination with all support functions like QA, QC, R&D, Purchase, marketing, etc.
- > Prepared database & maintain track of registration dossiers at various stages with close coordination with marketing team.

Cadila Pharmaceuticals Ltd., Dholka, Ahmedabad

Aug 2010 to Jan 2012

Project Executive (Project Coordinator), R&D-Project Management

Project Management of US/EU/ROW and Domestic Projects

Chirayu J. Pathak Page 3 of 6

- > Define Scope of Project, Goals and Deliverables that support business goals in collaboration with senior management, clients and stakeholders.
- ➤ Direct and manage project development program by co-ordination with F&D, ADL, RA, Purchase, warehouse, etc.
- > Preparing the development & launch plan status as per the project requirements and criticality.
- > Organizing the meetings with Cross-functional teams to facilitates issues' identification and resolution
- > Manage the critical path.
- > Proactively giving reminders to the concern departments for upcoming activities and timelines to be followed
- > Drive effective risks and issues to the management, ensuring processes are in place and effectively used.
- Monitoring the execution of Pilot/ Clinical/ Exhibit/ Commercial batches.
- > Instrumental in launching of DERMA Division.

Cadila Pharmaceuticals Ltd., Dholka, Ahmedabad

July 2009 to April 2010

Project Trainee, Formulation & Development

- > Exhaustive literature search.
- > Selection of suitable excipients, Preformulation studies, Selection of formulation strategies, design of experiments, selection of suitable equipments/instruments & formulation processes.
- Planning and execution stability batches.
- > Co-ordination with relevant departments' viz. ADL, Purchase, Warehouse, Manufacturing, QC, QA, Engineering, CRO.

Recognitions received at Zydus Cadila:

- Awarded 'Zydus First spirit' award for working beyond the line of work and supporting in attaining organization's cause in 2017.
- Awarded best project manager award for the year 2016 in February 2017 (first year of service)
- Received recognition for successful contribution in achieving annual target of cost savings projects assigned under 'PRISM' (operational excellence) for the year 2016-17 by manufacturing team.
- Received recognition for successful contribution in delivering highest cost savings project assigned under 'PRISM' (operational excellence) for the year 2017-18 by manufacturing team.
- Received 'Star Award' Q1-2019 for exemplary contribution & cross functional collaboration for execution of priority projects in 2018 (Reward and recognition initiative started by HR from 2019).
- Awarded best project manager award for the year 2018 in September 2019.

Chirayu J. Pathak Page 4 of 6

- Received 'Star Award' Q4 2019-20 for exemplary contribution & cross functional collaboration for execution of critical projects in 2019.
- Received 'Star Award' H2-2020 for exemplary contribution & cross functional collaboration for execution of key projects in 2020.

EDUCATION:

DEGREE	YEAR OF PASSING	%/DIVISION SECURED	NAME OF UNIVERSITY/BOARD
Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C)	2001	77%	Gujarat State Education Board
Higher Secondary School (H.S.C)	2003	52.65%	Gujarat State Higher Secondary Education Board
B.Pharm	2007	68 %	Rajiv Gandhi University of Health Sciences, Karnataka
M. Pharm (Industrial Pharmacy)	2010	69.35 %	Ganpat University, Kherva, Gujarat
Diploma in Management	2010	First Division	IGNOU, New Delhi
P.G.D.I.M (Post Graduate Diploma in Management)	2011	First Division	IGNOU, New Delhi
P.G.D.O.M (Post Graduate Diploma in Operations Management)	2012	First Division	IGNOU, New Delhi
Master of Business Administration (Operations Management)	2017	First Division	IGNOU, New Delhi

M.PHARM RESEARCH PROJECT:

Formulation, development and evaluation of novel solid dosage of Antimalarial Combination. Work carried out at Formulation Development department, Cadila Pharmaceuticals Ltd., Dholka, Ahmedabad.

CONFERENCES:

➤ Attended 6th Annual Pharma Project Management Conference from 22nd to 23rd February 2018 at Mumbai, organized by UMB India Pvt. Ltd.

CERTIFICATIONS:

- ➤ Certified course of "S-MSPro (MS project for Smart PM)" from SABCONS, Ahmedabad held from 24th to 25th September 2011.
- ➤ Certification for clearing 'National Level Pharmacy Talent Search Examination' held online (Senior level) on 18th March 2007.

Chirayu J. Pathak Page 5 of 6

KEY WORK SKILLS:

➤ Defining Project:

Carve up learning from other projects and laying down clear project objectives to attain success

➤ Project plan- Implementation and control:

Preparing work breakdown structure and Gantt chart, Identifying and managing anticipated risks,

Tracking monthly, quarterly project milestones completion

> Team building and management:

Motivating project team members to ensure project milestones are achieved

Tactfully handling and resolving team conflict

➤ Project communication skills:

Roper and timely communicating strategy change and management decisions to key stakeholders Have influencing skills to gain project buy-in, commitment and support from respective stakeholders

➤ Well versed with MS Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Project, Project Web Access (PWA) and SAP modules.

PERSONAL PROFILE:

Date of Birth : 16th January 1986

Sex : Male

Marital Status : Married

Child : One

Nationality : Indian

Languages known: English, Hindi, & Gujarati.

Hobbies & interest: Listening music, dancing, travelling & reading newspaper

REFERENCES:

References can be made available on request.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Chirayu J. Pathak Page 6 of 6